Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series IV is arranged in 4 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IV. CONVENTIONS
  - Sub-Series 203-0. Conventions
    - Complaint Chicago District Council, 1921 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      Dec. 4, 1921.
  - Sub-Series 203-1. Conventions
    - Resolutions Convention, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 33)
      Dec. 22, 1920.
  - Sub-Series 203-3. Conventions
    - 1921 Convention, 1920 (Box 15, Folder 34)
      Dec. 29, 1920.
  - Sub-Series 203-63. Conventions
    - Grand Lodge Convention. Los Angeles, California, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 1-9)
    - Grand Lodge Convention. Los Angeles, California, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Grand Lodge Convention. Los Angeles, California, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Resolutions referred to Committee on petitions and resolutions, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      Sept. 10, 1963.
    - Grand Lodge Convention. Los Angeles, California, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 13-14)
    - Grand Lodge Convention. Los Angeles, California, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Los Angeles, California Convention. Resolutions (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Grand Lodge Convention. Los Angeles, California, 1963 (Box 17, Folder 3-18)